# **Mohamed Refat**

Front End Developer

+201027561605 titorefat76@gmail.com github.com/refdd Egypt, cairo

#### SUMMARY

Coding on react and dreaming on react.js and next.js . Help companies to bulid complex web applications serving 1,000,000 users with React and modern technologies. Experience building functional and effective platforms, Fluency in javascript, HTML, and CSS

## EXPERIENCE

Front-end Development 08/2022 - Present

AroundEgyptTours

- · work part time there
- · I am building a website for tourist trips use nextjs ad tialwind css
- · and typescript

Front End Developer 03/2021 - Present

Osoule.com

- · create the user interface (UI) that determines what each part of
- seo optimization for websi
- · use pure javascript in react for built the website

Front-end Development 10/2021 - 02/2022

Tourzable KSA

- · seo optimization
- · styleing UI and UX make a responsive website and pages useing

pure javascript

### EDUCATION

Business 2020

benha university - Bachelor

## SKILLS

**JavaScript HOOKS** Redux React Next.js Jest **TypeScript** Git tailwindcss Node.js **HTML** NPM **CSS REST API** SCSS **Bootstrap**  Arabic English